(Sheldon:)...of never interfering
in your personal affairs.
(Leonard:)Yes, I've always admired that
about you.
(Sheldon:)As well you should.
(Sheldon:)But I'm going to make
an exception here.
(Leonard:)Oh, good.
(Sheldon:)Priya has moved back to India
to pursue her law career.
(Sheldon:)Instead of desperately trying to keep
this intercontinental relationship alive...
(Sheldon:)...you could use that time
to take up a hobby.
- A hobby?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)I read recently about a fellow in Kansas
with an enormous ball of twine.
(Sheldon:)I bet you could give him
a run for his money.
(Leonard:)You know, some people might say...
(Leonard:)...that it's great that we're trying
to make things work.
They'd say things like, "Love is stronger
than the miles between you."
(Sheldon:)When I rise to power,
those people will be sterilized.